Guide to the Cornell University Women's Studies Program records, 1968-1997.
Cornell University Women's Studies Program records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Women's Studies Program records, 1968-1997.
53-15-1585
Cornell University.Women's Studies Program.
ca. 22 cubic ft.
Correspondence, publications, printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of department faculty and speakers; course lists; seminars; annual reports and other material.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Women's Studies was renamed Feminist, Gender & Sexuality Studies (FGSS) in 2002.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of department faculty and speakers; course lists; seminars; annual reports; Advisory Group and other committee meetings; correspondence; yearly budgets; material concerning visiting scholars; and other records of the Women's Studies Program at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Bem, Sandra L.; Cornell University--Curricula.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.Women's Studies Program.
Subjects:
Women's studies.; Women--History.; Women--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Women - 1st Year, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Women - 1st Year, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Women - 1st Year, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (carbons), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Spring Courses, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Female Studies 101, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Information of Female Studies, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Human Development and Female Studies, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- English 482 Syllabus, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ED 470 Syllabus, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- AAUW, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Anti-Feminism, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Anti-Feminism, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Academic Women, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Academic Women, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Academic Women, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Children's Books and Toys, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Conferences on Women's Studies, 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Continuing Education, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Day Care, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- The Family and Sex, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Festival Clippings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Female Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Black Women, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Future of Female Studies, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Bibliographies and Lists of Reprints, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Intersession Conference on Women, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Media, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Council of Women, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- National Organization of Women (NOW) and Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- National Organization of Women (NOW) and Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- NOW, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Population Problems, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Religion, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- The Spokeswoman, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- General Women's Liberation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- General Women's Liberation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- General Women's Liberation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- General Women's Liberation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- SUNY - Women's Rights Caucus, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Third World Women, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- TV Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Washington Newsletter for Women, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- "Woman Activist", 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Women's Bureau, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Women's Bureau, 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Women's Centers, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Women's Liberation Movement, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- "Women Today", 1971 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Women and the Law, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- YWCA, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Bibliographies, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Bibliographies, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Bibliographies, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- HD and FS, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Women at Cornell - Survey, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Working Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Personnel, Payroll, and Budget, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Information for Mrs. Moll, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Positions Open at Other Universities and Colleges (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Women in Literature, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- April 12 Meeting, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Women in Education, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Research Projects, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Socialization (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Pictures - Historical figures (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Pictures - Historical figures (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Female Studies, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Africana Studies Center and Other Centers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Meetings with Dean Kahn, Plane, and EPC, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Knoblaugh Prize, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Accounts, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Monthly Budget-Accounting, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Kappa Alpha Theta Lectureship and Info on Possible Lecturers, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Course Syllabi for R. S. 375 - Spring, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Judy Laws Courses - Syllabi, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Record of Donations Given and Thank-You Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Female Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Female Studies Faculty Questionnaire, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Female Studies Faculty Questionnaire, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Female Studies Faculty Questionnaire, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Conference - not counted, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- "Future of Female Studies" Conference, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Lecture Notes - Psych 102 and History 354, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- F.S. 401 - Black and White Reprints, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Women's Bureau, US Dept. of Labor, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Letters to Doris Lessing, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Festival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Festival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Festival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Festival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Festival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Joan Panette (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Patricia Janovsky Photos (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Kathy Krathwohl Photos, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Appeal Letters, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Appeal Letters, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Article References and New Books (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Susan Bereaud, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Katherine Campbell (Box 2, Folder 38)
- News Clippings, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Syllabi (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Roster, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Research, Funding, and Proposal for Provost, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Sociology of the Female Labor Force, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Speakers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Women's Action Committee, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Women's Festival, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Society for the Humanities (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Search Committee - Academic Coordinator (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Structure (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Mrs. Moll, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Center for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Charter, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Communications, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Answered General Communications, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Conferences - Report from Conference on Women's Studies, Pittsburgh, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Cornell GLF - Penny Davis's Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Courses, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Curriculum Committee, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Cornell Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Alumni Requests for Funding (Dev. Office), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Advisory Board, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Affirmative Action, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Alumni Weekend, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- ETV Center, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Faculty Support Letters for Female Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Female Studies Conference, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Foundation Replies, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Funding Efforts, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Job Descriptions and Salaries (Box 2, Folder 69)
- ILR, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Journal of Female Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Directed Research Seminar, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Library Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Library Project - S. Tahsler, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Mailing List - Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Material for Dept. of Labor (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Florence Howe (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Janet Pool, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Press Release (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Proposal - NSF (Farley), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Proposal - Center for Research in Education, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Proposal - Provost Plane, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Proposal - Science Tech. and Society, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Proposal - Student Wives: Education Opportunities and Desired Family Size and Fertility, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Provost's Committee on Academic Women, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs Education Programs-McHugh, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Public Service, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Publications Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Publicity, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- New Letters for Stephanie, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Communications - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Affirmative Action, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Status of Women at University of Maryland, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Communiques on 1972-1973 (Plane), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Position Statements, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Structure, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Spring Courses, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Executive Committee Meetings, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Library, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- 401 Questionnaire - Rough Draft, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Female Studies - Summer Session, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Books - Order Forms, Publishers, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Letters Answered, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Letters Answered, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- English 482-Spring 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Phone Directories, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Female Studies Brochure, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Children's Media Program - Mandy, Sue B., and Cindy, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Curriculum Committee - Fall, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Other Existing Female Studies Programs, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Faculty Committee - Negotiations, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Mail to be answered, 1971-72 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- 401 Evaluation and Class Test, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Abortions and Other Health Problems, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Women's Films (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Female Studies Center vs. Interdisciplinary Program, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Jane Cambi's Letter, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Information on Women at Cornell - Coeds, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Extension/Public Service (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Speakers Bureau (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Female Studies, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Female Studies, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Final Report-Academic Coordinator, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Advisory Group Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Women's Study Advisory Group Committees, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Alumni Advisory, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Development Committee, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Lecture Series Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Library Committee, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Quota Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Service Extension Committee, 1972-73 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Educational-Audio-Visual, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Speaker's Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Curriculum Advisory Committee, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Cornell Conference on Women, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Anna Harrison, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Gloria Orenstein, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Alice Rossi, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Denise Scott Brown Venturi, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Katherine Walker, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Public Events, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Course Publicity, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Awards, Fellowships, Curriculum and Advisory, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Steering Committee Minutes, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Steering Committee Reports and Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Course syllabi, reading lists and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Female Studies 401 Paper, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Articles-Sources (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Articles-Sources (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Clippings, 1970-71 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ingrid Bengis-articles in Village Voice, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Other programs, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Female Studies-Publicity and Reports, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Stephanie Mauer Photos, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Photos (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Course Lists, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Course Lists, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Course Lists, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Course Lists, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Course Lists, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Course Lists, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Course Lists, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Courses, 1972-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Course Lists, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Course Lists, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Course Lists, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Course Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Course Lists, 1989-1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Fall - Friday Seminars, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Spring - Friday Seminars, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Fall - Friday Seminars, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Spring - Friday Seminars, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Fall - Friday Seminars, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Spring - Friday Seminars, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Friday Lecture Series - Jennie Farley, chair, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Jennie Farley, 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Carroll Smith-Rosenberg, Eve Sedgwick, Carol Gilligan, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Cornelia Bodea, Elizabeth Koontz, Rhona and Robert Rapoport, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Kathryn Moore, Rhoda Possen, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Lynne Abel, Constance Cook, Johanna Ettin, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Anita Racine, Beverly Tanenhaus, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Jane Camhi, Sarah Elbert, Debbie Jones, Carolyn Straughan, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Rachelle Taqqu, Carol Kammen, Rhoda Possen, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Muriel Fox, Shephard Aronson, Bonnie Buettner, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Barbara Richardson, Paula Vogel, Kathryn Walker, Margaret Wilder, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Judith Laws, Susan Rosenfeld, Alice Pempel, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Richard Lacayo, Maureen Turim, Nancy Henley, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Jane Donegan, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Jeanine Pirro, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Maxine Seller, Sheila Rowbotham, Marilyn Frye, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Maggie Scarf, Sandy and Daryl Bem, Joanne Fortune, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Adrienne Rich, Toshiko Sunada, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Evelyn Barish, Susan Brown Miller, Susan Sontag, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Elaine Showalter, Adrienne Rich, Michelle Rosaldo, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Carol Bellamy, Jessie Bernard, Kathryn Sklar, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Barbara Smith, Darlene Hine, Marilyn Frye, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Jane Gallop, Martha Vicinus, Audre Lorde, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Panel - Comparable Worth, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Panel - Women's issues in 1980 election (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Symposium - Women's issues, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Graduate Field Representative, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Visiting Scholars, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Mailing Lists, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Women in the Clergy, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Films, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Fellowships and Awards Committee - Flori Adkins, chair, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Curriculum and Advising Committee - Kathy March, chair, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Public Relations, Publicity, Outreach Committee - Rhoda Possen, chair, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Research Projects, Executive Board, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Women's Studies Directory, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Advertisements, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Job Descriptions, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Possible Upcoming Visitors, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Visitors, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Constitution for Faculty Board, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Faculty Board - General, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Teaching Faculty, 1977-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Candidates for Director, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Confidential Responses to letter - Sociology Search, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- CAU Women, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Revised Cranch Petition, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Cranch Response, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Dean Kahn - Women's Studies Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Visit of Princess of Iran, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Iran Clippings, Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Iran Clippings, Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Iran Publications, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Public Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Public Relations, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Foundations, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Ideas for Spring Friday Seminars, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Visiting Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Speakers Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Harry Levin, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Harry Levin, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Harry Levin, 1984-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Harry Levin, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Harry Levin, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Harry Levin, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Harry Levin, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Harry Levin, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Harry Levin, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Harry Levin, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- ERA March, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Round Table on Professionals, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Questionnaires - Sent to Faculty, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Questionnaires - Sent to Faculty, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Questionnaires - Sent to Faculty, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Long Range Planning Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Melon Fellow Information, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Affirmative Action, 1972-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Affirmative Action List, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Under Grad Representative Elections, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Inquiries about Women's Studies, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Information Sheets, 1978-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Evaluation Committee Material, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Becker Series, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Executive Board Vitas, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Lecturers Vitas, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Suggestions for Speakers, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Task Force on Centers and Programs, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Women in Business and Public Administration, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Sister's United, 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Campus Girl Scouts, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cornell Chorus, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Grad Women in Science, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Grad Wives, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Grad Women in Social Sciences, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Women's Law Coalition, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Friends of Human Ecology, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Society of Women Engineers, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Women's Caucus, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Campus Club, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Friend's of Women's Studies, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Women in Rural Development, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- National Endowment for Humanities, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Grants - Federal Register, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Cornell NOW, Ithaca NOW, Corning NOW, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- General Recruitment, 1973-1984 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Professional Skills Roster, 1967-1973 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Education Innovation Gift, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Performing Arts Series, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- COSEP, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Space for Women's Studies Program, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Cook Scholarship Fund, Smith Memorial Fund, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- CU Council Women Trustees, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Dean Seznec, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Barbara Richardson Evaluation, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Title IX of the Educational Amendment, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- TC3 Women's Studies, 1979-1986 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Upstate Women's Studies Program, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Trustee Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Provosts Committee, 1973-1984 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Measuring Change in Status of Women Workers, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Women at Cornell, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Undergrad Studies/Independent, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Prizes and Awards, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Senate Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Syllabi, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- University Libraries, 1971-1976 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Library Committee, 1975-1987 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Taqqu and March Proposal, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Louise Lamphere class action vs. Brown U. (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Elena Cornaro, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Mary Ott Report, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Katherine Houpt, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Buttrick - Crippen Fellowship, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Women's Studies - Sandra Bem, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Sandra Bem Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Sandra Bem Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Women's Studies: Aidelberg, Bowers, Brown, Berlant, Bohmer, Blackall, 1979-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Women's Studies: Brumberg, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Women's Studies:Beckwith, Buck-Morss, Chaves, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Women's Studies: Cohen, de Bary, Dugas, Dudden, Ezergailis, Easton, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Women's Studies: Farley, Fried, Fortune, Goldsmith, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Women's Studies: March/Holmberg, Isbell, Jacobus, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Women's Studies:Jebb, Ormondroyd, Winterkorn, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Women's Studies: Jones and Straughan, R. Levin, Katzenstein, 1977-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Women's Studies: K. March, 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Women's Studies: McConnell-Ginet, McKee, Meyers, Mohanty, Possen, Purdy, 1973-1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Women's Studies: Rosecrance, Siegel, Tanenhaus, Williams, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Executive Board Meeting, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Executive Board, 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Executive Board, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Executive Board Elections, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Executive Board Elections, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Board Meetings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Board Meetings, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Board Meetings, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Board Meetings, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Board Meetings, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Board Meetings, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Nominations: Women's Studies Executive Board, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Lecturers on Executive Board, 1968-1977 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Faculty Board, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Faculty Board Elections, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Conferene: Dealing with Difference, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)